Horlacher, John Arbitration Records 5587
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Standard Register Co. vs. Int'l. Printing Pressmen of N.A., Local 594, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 47a)
- Stanley Electric Mfg. Co. vs. IBEW, Local 2007, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  Issue: layoff - recall
- Stauffer Chem. Co. vs. IBT, Local 929, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 48a)
  Issue: premium pay, Sat., Sun. & holiday work.
- Sterling Faucet Co. vs. USW, Local 6214, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  Issue: management rights - contracting out.
- Stern & Co. vs. IBT, Local 107, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Stone Container Corp. vs. IBPSPMW, Local 375, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  Issue: termination of employment - leaves of absence.
- Strick Co. vs. AUW; vs. UAW, Local 1354, 1958-1967 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  Issue: termination of employment - discharge vs. quit; arbitrability, fringe benefits -insurance & medical plans, assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Struthers-Dunn, Inc. vs. IUE, Local 140, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  Issue: workweek - reduction.
- Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 802, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Issue: assignment of jobs; discipline discharge.
- Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 802, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Issue: union representatives & union business - replacement stewards, discipline discharge, working conditions - past practice.
- Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 802, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Issue: discipline discharge; discipline warning; absences..
- Sun Building & Dry Dock Co. vs. Marine Draftsmen's Assoc; vs. IBBISBFH, 1968-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Issue: union representatives and business, assignment of jobs - new equipment, assignment of jobs discrimination, assignment of jobs - remedy for improper assignment, suspension -following - following reinstatement.
- Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. Marine Draftsmen's Assoc; vs. IBBISBFH, Lodge 802, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Issue: fringe benefits - insurance & medical plans, discipline - discharge.
- Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. vs. IBBISBFH, Lodge 802, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Superior Paint and Varnish Co. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime; rates of pay - Saturday, Sunday & holiday pay.
- Superior Paper Products Co. vs. IBPSPHW, Local 350, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Swanee Paper Co. vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Issue: rates of pay -premium pay
- Synthane Taylor Corp., Valley Forge Division vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Issue: management rights - operation of the business.
- Tactair Fluid Controls Corp. vs. UAW, Local 416, 1962-1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Issue: arbitration procedure - multiple grievances; rates of pay - shift differentials; assignment of jobs - failure to assign.
- Taft Broadcasting Co. (WTAF-TV), vs. IBEW, Local 1241, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Taylor Fibre Co. vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1956-1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  Issue: overtime - failure to assign; overtime - notice; management rights - shift scheduling, assignment of jobs - failure to assign; reduction in force seniority; vacancies seniority; vacancies - ability vs. seniority; bidding - right to bid; bidding
- Taylor Lock Co. vs. IUE, Local 123, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Technitrol, Inc. vs. IUE, Loci 149, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Issue: vacation pay - layoff.
- Teleflex, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 1039, 1967-1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  Issue: termination of employment - following illness or physical disability; discipline discharge; contracting out - management rights; assignment of jobs - rates of pay.
- Teleflex, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 644; Temple University Hospital vs. Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, District 1199C., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Issue: bidding qualifications, discipline - discharge.
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 8-638, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 8-638, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Titan Metal Mfg. Co. vs. UAW, Local 1282, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Trailmobile, a division of Pullman, Inc. vs. IBBISBFH, Local 347, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Issue: discipline -walkout.
- Treadwell Engineering Co. vs. USW, Local 2338, 1955-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - claim for pay of higher classification, rates of pay - overtime; discipline.
- Triangle Publications, Inc. Cases, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Issue: discipline suspension, contracts - effective date, assignment of jobs overtime, rates of pay - premium pay.
- Troy Laundry Co., Inc. vs. Amalgamated. Clothing Workers of Amer., Laundry, Dry Cleaning & Linen Supply Workers Union, Local 686, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Issue: rates of pay -increases; vacations & vacation pay; bonuses.
- Tung-sol electric, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1497, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Issue: fringe benefits - pension plans.
- Two Guys, Inc. - Vornado, Inc. vs. Amalgamated. Meat Cutters, Local 56, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Issue: discipline -suspension; discipline - demotion.
- Union Hills Paper Mfg. Co. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers, Local 509, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Issue: Mgt. Rights - reorganization of job classifications.
- United Air Lines, Inc. vs. Int'l. Air Line Pilots Assoc, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Issue: crew size - safety.
- United Container Co. vs. IBPSPMW, Local 375, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Issue: reporting pay - lack of work, discipline - discharge.
- United Engineers & Constructors, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Issue: suspensions - pending court action, assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit.
- United Markets, Inc. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- United News Transportation Co. vs. Philadelphia Newspaper & Magazine Chauffeurs & Handlers, Local 628, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- United Parcel Service, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 804, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Issue: termination of employment - self-induced, bidding - qualifications.
- United States Asbestos Division of Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc. vs. UTWA, Local 2590, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Issue: arbitrability; rates of pay - increases; rates of pay - incentive pay.
- United States Ceramic Tile Co. vs. UGCW, Local 45, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Issue: vacation pay; rates of pay.
- United States Gauge Division of America Machine & Metals, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 135 and Amer. Fed. of Technical Engineers, Local 117; United States Gauge, Division of AMETEK, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 1092, 1962-1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit, contracting out -bargaining unit work.
- United States Hoffman Machinery Corp. vs. IAM, Local Lodge, #847, District Lodge #128, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Issue: seniority - recall.
- U.S. Industrial Chemicals Co. vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Paperworkers Int'l. Union, Philadelphia, Local 286, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Issue: management rights - crew size; arbitrability.
- United States Pipe L Foundry Co. vs. USW, Local 2026, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Univac Division of Sperry Rand Corp. vs. IUE, Local 165, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Universal-Rundle Corp. vs. Industrial Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers, Local 75, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Issue: severance pay - eligibility.
- Upper Southampton Township vs. Upper Southampton Township Police (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Issue: arbitration -interest arbitration.
- Upper Southampton Township vs. Upper Southampton Township Police (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Veit & Young, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 181, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Issue: discharge - apprentice - insubordination.
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1965-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Issue: retroactive pay, quit -reinstatement following, (draft), discharge - union activity, insubordination, subcontracting.
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Issue: overtime - merit of claim (includes exhibits, draft, briefs).
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Issue: vacations - computation (includes draft, briefs, notes & exhibits).
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Issue: discharge - assault, job classification (includes exhibits, briefs & notes).
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Issue: discharge - unsatisfactory work (includes exhibits, notes, briefs).
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Issue: dual classification work, (draft, notes, briefs).
- Vertol Division of Boeing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1069, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Issue: method of recall (includes notes, briefs, drafts, exhibit).
- Vornado, Inc., Two Guys vs. Retail Clerks Local 1360, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Issue: discharge, conspiracy, unauthorized taking of property (Includes drafts, notes).
- Vornado, Inc., Two Guys vs. ILGWU, Local 220, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Issue: discharge - misappropriation (includes draft, notes, exhibits).
- Walben, Inc. vs. Northeast Independent Aircraft Products Assoc, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Issue: discipline -discharge; discipline - reprimands.
- Walker Brothers vs. IBEW, Local BA 1088, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Issue: recall - ability vs. seniority, rates of pay; layoff -seniority.
- Warner Co. vs. Int'l. Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 830, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Issue: holiday pay; vacations, discipline suspension, discipline - discharge.
- Warminster, Town of vs. Warminster Township Police, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Issue: arbitration - interest arbitration.
- Washington Post Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, AFL-CIO, Washington Newspaper Guild, 1958-1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Issue: arbitrability - timeliness; termination of employment - severance pay, fringe benefits - insurance & medical plans.
- Washington Post Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, AFL-CIO, Washington Newspaper Guild, 1958-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Washington Publishers Assoc. vs. Columbia Typographical Union, #101, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Issue: sick leave - eligibility - sick leave.
- Wayne Pump Co. vs. UAW, 1957-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Issue: management rights - change of work schedule; discipline suspension, vacation pay, layoff - seniority; rates of pay, overtime equalization, funeral leave & funeral pay, discipline discharge, reinstatement - refusal; termination of employment -
- Western Electric Co., Inc. (Allentown Works) vs. IBEW, Local 1522, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - failure to assign.
- Western Stevedoring Co. vs. Amalgamated. Tobacco, Food & Allied Workers, Local 1711, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Westfield River Paper Co. vs. Glassine Paper Workers, Local 99, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Issue: vacation pay; holidays & holiday pay.
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Theatrical & Stage Employees, Local 804, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Issue: jurisdiction - crossing craft lines.
- Weyerhaeuser Co. - Container Division, Barrington Plant Cases, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Issue: crew size - past practice, lunch periods - worked lunch period, discipline discharge, vacations - scheduling; shutdown - vacation shutdown.
- Wheaton Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 219, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - leaders.
- White, J.H. Inc. vs. UAW, Local 416, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Issue: arbitrability - survival of contract rights.
- Whitman, Stephen F. 1 Son, Inc. vs. Bakery & Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union, Local 439, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Issue: termination of employment - discharge v. quits, discipline - discharge.
- Wicaco Machine Corp. vs. IUE, Local 147, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Wickes Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Wickes Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 676, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Wildstein & Sons, M. vs. IBT, Local 929, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Wilkening Mfg. Co. vs. UAW, Local 416, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Issue: layoff seniority, arbitrability; recall seniority, discipline - discharge.
- Williamson Veneer Co. vs. United Furniture Workers of America, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Williamsport Bus Co. vs. Amalgamated Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coash Employees of America, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  Issue: arbitrability; vacation pay - quits.
- Wilmington, City of ve. AFSCME Locals, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  Issue: contract interpretation - illness provision, arbitrability - assignment of jobs, assignment of jobs -discrimination.
- Wilson Freight Forwarding Inc. vs. Highway Truck Drivers & Helpers, Local 107, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Woods, T. B. Sons & Co. vs. UAW, Local 695, 1962-1967 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work, absences - discipline.
- Yale & Towne, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 1717, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  Issue: discipline discharge, assignment of jobs seniority, assignment of jobs - temporary assignment, discipline - discharge.
- Yale & Towne, Inc. and Yale & Towne Mfg. Co. vs. IAM, Lodge 1717; vs. OPEIU Local 14, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  Issue: strikes, slowdowns & work stoppages recall, recall - following strike, assignment of jobs - following recall.
- York Bus Co. vs. Amalgamated. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of Amer., Local 858, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  Issue: contract interpretation.
- York Gazette Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, Local 218, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Issue: contract modification -interest arbitration.
- York-Hoover Corp., Body Division vs. UAW, Local 1079, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  Issue: rates of pay - merit increase, union representatives & business - resignation from union.
- Young & Co., J.S. vs. OCAW, Local 8-675, 1963-1971 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  Issue: discipline discharge, transfers - lack of work transfer.
- Zabel Brothers vs. Amalgamated. Lithographers & Photoengravers Int'l. Union, Local 14-L, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 33)